Guide to the Group Material Archive 1976-2009 (bulk 1979-1996) MSS.215
Fales Library and Special Collections
- Series VI: Photographic Material, 204542
  - "Democracy Poll" photos, 1990; 206796 (Box 10, Folder 15)
  - "Your Message Here" Photos, 1990; 206792 (Box 10, Folder 16)
  - "AIDS Timeline" Photos and Negatives, 1990; 206793 (Box 10, Folder 17)
  - "Cash Prize" Photos of Ads, 1991; 206778 (Box 10, Folder 18)
  - "Democracy Wall" for Boston Photos, 1993-1994; 206794 (Box 10, Folder 19)
  - Photo Album - Julie Ault GM 1994-1995, 206795 (Box 10, Folder 20)
  - "Market", 1995; 206797 (Box 10, Folder 21)
  - Campaign Slides, undated; 206798 (Box 10, Folder 22)
  - "DA ZI BAOS" @ Damon Brandt, undated; 206799 (Box 10, Folder 23)
  - Miscellaneous Slides, Photos and Negatives, undated; 206800 (Box 10, Folder 24)
  - Negatives - "Black and white and other prints", undated; 206801 (Box 10, Folder 25)
  - From Binder 1 (1 of 1) - "Subculture", originals, 1981-1986; 206802 (Box 11)
  - From Binder 1 (2 of 2) - Originals: "Constitution", "AIDS Timeline", "Your Message Here", "Tomorrow", 1987-1993; 206803 (Box 12)
  - From Binder 2 (1 of 2) - Dupes: "Inserts", "Democracy", "Your Message Here", "Bus Projects", "Shopping Bag", "AIDS Timeline", "Cash Prize", "MFA", "Market", 1987-1990; 206804 (Box 13)
  - From Binder 2 (1 of 2) - Dupes: "Inserts", "Democracy", "Your Message Here", "Bus Projects", "Shopping Bag", "AIDS Timeline", "Cash Prize", "MFA", "Market", 1987-1990; 206805 (Box 14)
  - From Binder 3 (1 of 2) - Dupes: "First Year", "DA ZI BAOS", "Subculture", "Timeline", "Wales", "MASS", "Messages To Washington", "Americana", Arts + Leisure", "Constitution", "Anti-Baudrillard", "The Castle", 1980-1986; 206806 (Box 15)
  - From Binder 3 (2 of 2) - Dupes: "First Year", "DA ZI BAOS", "Subculture", "Timeline", "Wales", "MASS", "Messages To Washington", "Americana", Arts + Leisure", "Constitution", "Anti-Baudrillard", "The Castle", 1985-1987; 206807 (Box 16)
  - From Binder 4 (1 of 2) - Original slides 1st year-1980 Through 1985 ("Americana"), 1980 - 1989; 206808 (Box 17)
  - From Binder 4 (2 of 2) - Original slides 1st year-1980 Through 1985 ("Americana"), 1981 - 1986; 206809 (Box 18)
  - Show and Tell photographs - 1 of 2, undated; 210265 (Box 60)
  - Show and Tell photographs - 2 of 2, undated; 210266 (Box 61)
- Series VII: Video recordings, 208842
  This series contains video recordings collected by Group Material. Items are arranged chronologically by date of creation, and then alphabetically by title. Material includes video documentation of Group Material projects, news coverage, and video included in exhibitions. Descriptions are derived from the original videocassette or container annotations and include title, date, the original format of video, and the duration).
  - Subseries A: Video recordings, 210783
    - Video Hypnosis-Successful Independent Lifestyle, 1988; ID: 215.0001; 210791 (Box 31, Media ID: 215.0001)
      Physical Characteristics and Technical Requirements
      Duration: 30 minutes
      Original format: VHS
      Conditions Governing Access
      Currently unavailable until duplication occurs.
    - Group Material @ Austin, 1989; ID: 215.0002; 210785 (Box 31, Media ID: 215.0002, Case 215.0002)
      Duration: 2 hours 1 minute
      Currently available.
      Existence and Location of Copies
      DVD access copy available.
    - They are lost to vision altogether - Tom Kalin, 1989; ID: 215.0004; 210787 (Box 31, Case 215.0004)
      Duration: 18 minutes
    - Whitney Houston - The Star Spangled Banner, 1991; ID: 215.0005; 210789 (Box 31, Media ID: 215.0005)
      Duration: 5 minutes
    - Voices from the Front, 1991; ID: 215.0006; 210788 (Box 31, Media ID: 215.0006)
    - [Group Material Video Kahsley-"Market"], 1993; ID: 215.0007; 210790 (Box 31, Media ID: 215.0007)
      - Images of the 80s, 1989; 210786 (Box 31, Object ID: 215.0003)
        Duration: 00:52:00
        Original Format: VHS
        Currently unavailable.
    - Christian Action Network, 1994; ID: 215.0008; 210792 (Box 31, Media ID: 215.0008)
    - Kunstverein: Cops, March 5, 1995; ID: 215.0037; 253912 (Box 31, Case 215.0037)
      Duration: 1 hour
      Original format: VHS (PAL Standard)
    - Kunstverein: Video Hypnosis, March 5, 1995; ID: 215.0038; 253913 (Box 31, Case 215.0038)
      Duration: 29 minute
    - Kunstverein: Value Visions, March 5, 1995; ID: 215.0039; 253914 (Box 31, Case 215.0039)
      Duration: 1 hour 35 minutes
    - Cops Caught in the Act, 1996; ID: 215.0009; 210793 (Box 31, Media ID: 215.0009)
      Duration: 50 minutes
    - Bridge - PAL Standard, 1997; ID: 215.0010; 210794 (Box 31, Media ID: 215.0010)
      Duration: 26 minutes
    - Bridge - NTSC Standard (Copy), 1997; ID: 215.0013; 210797 (Box 31, Case 215.0013)
    - Julie Ault - Oral History, February 3, 2011; ID: 215.0040; 253915 (Box 31, Case 215.0040)
      Duration: 49 minutes
      Original format: MiniDV
    - Blank, undated; ID: 215.0011; 210795 (Box 31, Media ID: 215.0011)
    - Blank, undated; ID: 215.0012; 210796 (Box 31, Media ID: 215.0012)
    - Group Material, undated; ID: 215.0014; 210798 (Box 31, Media ID: 215.0014)
      Same content as ID: 215.0018
    - How To Organize your Home for "Market", undated; ID: 215.0015; 210799 (Box 31, Media ID: 215.0015)
      Duration: 38 minutes
    - Island Rehearsal - 1. Assort TV, 2.GM "Subculture" News, 3. "Artists Call" News., undated; ID: 215.0017; 210800 (Box 31, Case 215.0017)
      Duration: 28 minutes
    - Oberlin Piece - Group Material, undated; ID: 215.0018; 210801 (Box 31, Case 215.0018)
      Duration: 24 minutes
    - What Follows...Julie Ault, undated; ID: 215.0019; 210802 (Box 31, Case 215.0019)
      Duration: 31 minutes
    - Lifestyles of the Rich & Famous, undated; ID: 215.0020; 210803 (Box 31, Media ID: 215.0020)
      Original format: U-matic
    - Images of the 80s/PSAs-Direct Effect & Gran Fury - "Kissing Doesn't Kill..."/Whitney Houston, undated; ID: 215.0021; 210804 (Box 31, Media ID: 215.0021)
    - DiAna's Hair Ego: AIDS Info Up Front/Abortion for Survival, undated; ID: 215.0022; 210805 (Box 31, Case 215.0022)
      Duration: 60 minutes
- Series VIII: Sound recordings, 210781
  This series contains audio recordings collected by Group Material. Items are arranged chronologically. Material includes original audiocassettes created for "Liberty and Justice" and "Unisex," as well as audio documentation of Group Material's events and exhibitions.
  Descriptions are derived from the original audiocassette or container annotations and include title, date, and format.
  - Subseries A: Sound recordings, 211411
    - "Liberty & Justice" Soundtrack - Group Material, 1986; ID:215.0024; 210810 (Box 31, Media ID:215.0024)
      Original format: 1/4" audiocassette
    - Unisex - Group Material - The Center Show - Dupe #1, 1989; ID: 215.0025; 210811 (Box 31, Media ID: 215.0025)
    - Group Material - (Unisex) - Disco, 1989; ID: 215.0026; 210812 (Box 31, Media ID: 215.0026)
    - The Castle, undated; ID: 215.0027; 210813 (Box 31, Media ID: 215.0027, Case 215.0027)
      CD access copy available.
    - Cultural Participation - Roundtable - 1, undated; ID: 215.0028; 210814 (Box 31, Media ID: 215.0028)
    - Cultural Participation - Roundtable - 2, undated; ID: 215.0029; 210815 (Box 31, Media ID: 215.0029)
    - Cultural Participation - Roundtable - 3, undated; ID: 215.0030; 210816 (Box 31, Media ID: 215.0030)
    - Americana / Group Material Master, undated; ID: 215.0031; 210817 (Box 31, Media ID: 215.0031)
      Currently unavailable until format occurs.
    - Group Material - Da Zi Baos, undated; 215.0032; 210818 (Box 31, Cassette 215.0032, E-records fales_mss215, E-records 215.0032)
      Original format: 1/4" audiocassette, Duration: 90 min.
      Preservation note: "Side 2: 00:06:15;xx-00:46:30;xx [end] Content unrelated to to the subject matter of the tape - not included on access copy."
    - Politics and Election Round and Table #1, undated; ID: 215.0033; 210819 (Box 31, Media ID: 215.0033)
      Currently unavailable until duplicatio occurs.
    - Politics and Election Round and Table #2, undated; ID: 215.0034; 210820 (Box 31, Media ID: 215.0034)
    - Blank, undated; ID: 215.0035; 210821 (Box 31, Media ID: 215.0035)
    - Secrets of Washington, undated; ID: 215.0036; 210822 (Box 31, Media ID: 215.0036)
- Series IX: Computer Disks, 210823
  This series contains four CD-Rs and one DVD from the Group Material collection. The items are arranged by format, and then chronologically. Descriptions are derived from the original item annotations and include title, date, and the original format of media.
  - Subseries IX.A: Access Copies, 211412
  - Subseries IX.B: Originals, 211413
    - Documenta 1-9, undated; 210824 (Box 31, Folder ID: 215.3.0001)
      Format: CD-R
    - Documenta 1-9, undated; 210825 (Box 31, Folder ID: 215.3.0002)
    - Ashford [Mohaiemen], undated; 210826 (Box 31, Folder ID: 215.3.0003)
    - 3 Miscellaneous images from DA's [Doug Ashford's] House, undated; 210827 (Box 31, Folder ID: 215.3.0004)
    - Unisex, undated; 210828 (Box 31, Folder ID: 215.3.0005)
      Format: DVD-R
- Series X: Objects, 205985
  This series is comprised of artworks, artifacts, and ephemera from the Group Material Archive. The Positive Art "Life Masks" were originally exhibited in "AIDS Timeline."
  - "AIDS Timeline" - [Exhibited Material] - Reagan/Bush campaign button - "The time is now.", [1980]; 210831 (Box 26, Object ID: 215.2.0001)
  - "AIDS Timeline" - [Exhibited Material] - Reagan in '80 campaign button., 1980; 210832 (Box 26, Object ID: 215.2.0002)
  - Primer Aniversario de la Revolucion Popular Sandinista-scroll (rolled) - 1 of 2, 1980; 210850 (Box 27, Object ID: 215.2.0003)
  - Primer Aniversario de la Revolucion Popular Sandinista-scroll (rolled) - 2 of 2, 1980; 210851 (Box 27, Object ID: 215.2.0004)
  - "Eat This Show" - Three paper plate exhibition announcements, 1981; 210840 (Box 28, Object ID: 215.2.0005)
  - "AIDS Timeline" - [Exhibited Material] - "That's What Friends are for" - Dionne & Friends - 45 rpm record., 1985; 210833 (Box 26, Object ID: 215.2.0006)
  - Keith Haring Shopping Bag [Exhibited Material], [1985]; 210857 (Box 28, Object ID: 215.2.0007)
  - T-shirt - Tim Rollins and K.O.S. For Artists Space - [Source Material], 1987; 207568 (Box 29, Object ID: 215.2.0008)
  - "Untitled" - Nancy Linn - Framed black and white photograph of little girl, 1987; 210903 (Box 54, Object ID: 215.2.0012)
  - Artwork by Teresa Bramlette - "For Julie Ault and Andres Serrano", 1988; 210864 (Box 28, Object ID: 215.2.0009)
  - "Democracy: Cultural Participation" - [Exhibited Material] - American Flag with image of Biker, 1988; 210839 (Box 28, Object ID: 212.2.0010)
  - One copy of "Inserts" in original newspaper, 1988; 205980 (Box 30, Object ID: 215.2.0011)
  - "AIDS Timeline" - Positive Art "Life Masks" project by Sharon Siskin - Artist-Eddie Booker, 1989; 209374 (Box 22, Object ID: 215.2.0013)
  - "AIDS Timeline" - Positive Art "Life Masks" project by Sharon Siskin - Artist-Jim Greblowski, 1989; 209375 (Box 22, Object ID: 215.2.0014)
  - "AIDS Timeline" - Positive Art "Life Masks" project by Sharon Siskin - Artist-Randy Lou, 1989; 209376 (Box 22, Object ID: 215.2.0015)
  - "AIDS Timeline" - Positive Art "Life Masks" project by Sharon Siskin - Artist-Anonymous (red, white and blue), 1989; 209377 (Box 22, Object ID: 215.2.0016)
  - "AIDS Timeline" - Positive Art "Life Masks" project by Sharon Siskin - Artist-Steve Curd, 1989; 209382 (Box 23, Object ID: 215.2.0017)
  - "AIDS Timeline" - Positive Art "Life Masks" project by Sharon Siskin - Artist-Barry Frederick, 1989; 209383 (Box 23, Object ID: 215.2.0018)
  - "AIDS Timeline" - Positive Art "Life Masks" project by Sharon Siskin - Artist-Ken Huff, 1989; 209384 (Box 23, Object ID: 215.2.0019)
  - "AIDS Timeline" - Positive Art "Life Masks" project by Sharon Siskin - Artist-Max Proudfoot, 1989; 209385 (Box 23, Object ID: 215.2.0020)
  - "AIDS Timeline" - Positive Art "Life Masks" project by Sharon Siskin - Artist-Ken Huff, 1989; 209386 (Box 24, Object ID: 215.2.0021)
  - "AIDS Timeline" - Positive Art "Life Masks" project by Sharon Siskin - Artist-Ken Huff, 1989; 209387 (Box 24, Object ID: 215.2.0022)
  - "AIDS Timeline" - Positive Art "Life Masks" project by Sharon Siskin - Artist-JJ, 1989; 209413 (Box 24, Object ID: 215.2.0023)
  - "AIDS Timeline" - Positive Art "Life Masks" project by Sharon Siskin - Artist-Steve Brown, 1989; 209414 (Box 24, Object ID: 215.2.0024)
  - "AIDS Timeline" - Positive Art "Life Masks" project by Sharon Siskin - Artist-Paul Freitas, 1989; 209416 (Box 25, Object ID: 215.2.0025)
  - "AIDS Timeline" - Positive Art "Life Masks" project by Sharon Siskin - Artist-Gary Ostrander, 1989; 209415 (Box 25, Object ID: 215.2.0026)
  - "AIDS Timeline" - Positive Art "Life Masks" project by Sharon Siskin - Artist-Richard McMullen, 1989; 209417 (Box 25, Object ID: 215.2.0027)
  - "AIDS Timeline" - Positive Art "Life Masks" project by Sharon Siskin - Artist-David Taylor, 1989; 209436 (Box 55, Object ID: 215.2.0028)
  - "AIDS Timeline" - Positive Art "Life Masks" project by Sharon Siskin - Artist-Jim Greblowski, 1989; 209437 (Box 55, Object ID: 215.2.0029)
  - "AIDS Timeline" - [Source Material] - "We're All Living With AIDS" button., 1989; 210834 (Box 26, Object ID: 215.2.0030)
  - "AIDS Timeline" - [Source Material] - Lifestyles condom, [1989-1990]; 210835 (Box 26, Object ID: 215.2.0031)
  - "AIDS Timeline" - [Exhibited Material] - magazine display case - red, [1989-1990]; 210849 (Object ID: 215.2.0032)
  - "AIDS Timeline" - [Exhibited Material] - magazine display case - blue, [1989-1990]; 210866 (Object ID: 215.2.0033)
  - "AIDS Timeline" - [Exhibited Material] - men's tie with American flag pattern, [1989-1990]; 210837 (Box 26, Object ID: 215.2.0034)
  - "AIDS Timeline" - [Exhibited Material] - Silencio=Muerte t-shirt, [1989-1990]; 210836 (Box 29, Object ID: 215.2.0035)
  - "AIDS Timeline" - [Exhibited Material] - Tylenol bottle, [1989-1990]; 210838 (Box 26, Object ID: 215.2.0036)
  - "AIDS Timeline" - [Exhibited Material] - yellow rubber gloves, [1989-1990]; 210830 (Box 26, Object ID: 215.2.0037)
  - T-shirt - Spero, Nancy - for Artists' Space, 1989; 207685 (Box 29, Object ID: 215.2.0038)
  - Carrie Mae Weems- Maroon ceramic plate with flowers and image of back of woman's head., 1990; 210845 (Box 58, Object ID: 215.2.0057)
  - "Cash Prize" - Dynasty image - "Family Photo" - mounted [Exhibited Material], 1991; 210847 (Box 27, Object ID: 215.2.0039)
  - T-shirt - B. Wurtz - [Source Material] - "T" outline on puce t-shirt, 1991; 207694 (Box 29, Object ID: 215.2.0040)
  - "Market" - [Source Material] - Product Presentation - Communication Control Systems International, 1993; 210859 (Box 59, Object ID: 215.2.0041)
  - "Market" catalog - 1 of 2, 1995; 205979 (Box 33, Object ID: 215.2.0042)
    This catalog includes one plastic bag, containing one printed booklet, one "Keep-It" clip, one bumper sticker, and one letter opener.
  - "Market" catalog - 2 of 2, 1995; 205978 (Box 33, Object ID: 215.2.0043)
    This catalog includes one plastic bag, containing one printed booklet, one bumper sticker, and one letter opener. This catalog is missing one "Keep-It" clip.
  - Group Material Seal, undated; 205733 (Box 33, Object ID: 215.2.0044)
  - Set of Who, What, Where, When, and Why stamps + Group Material stamp, undated; 205734 (Box 33, Object ID: 215.2.0045)
  - Slogan Notepads [Source Material], undated; 210858 (Box 33, Object ID: 215.2.0046)
  - T-shirt - "Vietnam War Ads..." ARKIPELAG, neon pink text on white shirt, 1998; 207686 (Box 29, Object ID: 215.2.0047)
  - T-shirt - ACT UP - large black logo on white shirt, undated; 207567 (Box 32, Object ID: 215.2.0048)
  - T-shirt - ACT UP - "Health Care Not Warfare" - black text on white shirt, undated; 207565 (Box 32, Object ID: 215.2.0049)
  - T-shirt - ACT UP - "Planet Earth" - black text on white shirt - continental map on back, undated; 207566 (Box 32, Object ID: 215.2.0050)
  - T-shirt - Holzer, Jenny - "Abuse of Power Comes as No Surprise" - black text on white shirt, undated; 207683 (Box 32, Object ID: 215.2.0051)
  - T-shirt - Holzer, Jenny - "Abuse of Power Comes as No Surprise" - red text on white shirt, undated; 207684 (Box 32, Object ID: 215.2.0052)
  - T-shirt - Jenkins, Michael - skull and cross bones on marigold, undated; 207695 (Box 34, Object ID: 215.2.0053)
  - T-shirt - Kruger, Barbara - "I shop therefore I am", undated; 207569 (Box 34, Object ID: 215.2.0054)
  - T-shirt - Kruger, Barbara - "Your Body is a Battleground", undated; 207682 (Box 34, Object ID: 215.2.0055)
  - T-shirt - 15 reasons why a beer is better than a woman, undated; 207696 (Box 34, Object ID: 215.2.0056)
  - Wallet - "Freedom", undated; 231741 (Box 34, Object ID: 215.2.0059)
  - Clip - "Freedom", undated; 231742 (Box 34, Object ID: 215.2.0060)
- Oversize Series I: Project Files, 204548
  This series contains oversize materials from Series I: Project Files. This includes exhibited material, source material, exhibition announcements, fliers, posters, diagrams, plans, and original artworks related to Group Material projects.
  Notable artworks include the original "Subculture" subway panels created by individual artists for exhibition in IRT subway trains, the square panels created by individual artists for the exhibition "MASS", and the original newspaper advertisement for "Cash Prize."
  - Mushroom Cloud Poster, 1967; 216159 (Folder 19)
  - "The United States of Atticus" Poster, April 15, 1972; 216160 (Folder 6 Left)
  - "Times Square Show" Poster, 1980; 216164 (Folder 4 Left)
  - "Group Material Opens October 4" Inaugural Exhibition posters, 1980; 210928 (Folder 7 Right)
  - Training for Leisure - The Kitchen, 1980; 210929 (Box 39, Folder 2)
  - "AIDS Timeline" - [Source Material] - Mike Glier - "White Male Power", 1981; 210930 (Box 39, Folder 3)
  - The Cooper Pioneer Newspaper, March 4, 1982; 210931 (Box 39, Folder 4)
  - "Subculture" - Poster Strips [2], September 1983; 216154 (Folder 9 Right)
  - "Artists Call Against Intervention in Central America" Poster [2], January 1984; 216161 (Folder 13)
  - "AIDS Timeline" [Source Material] - Army National Guard Advertisement, 1985; 211163 (Box 51, Folder 1)
  - "Messages to Washington" [Exhibition Material] - posters, 1985; 211164 (Box 51, Folder 2)
  - "MASS" - panels 1-20, 1985-1986; 210971 (Box 43)
  - "MASS" - panels 21-40, 1985-1986; 210972 (Box 44)
  - "MASS" - panels 41-60, 1985-1986; 210973 (Box 45)
  - "MASS" - panels 61-78, 1985-1986; 210974 (Box 46)
  - "MASS" - panels 79-100, 1985-1986; 210975 (Box 47)
  - "MASS" - panels 101-124, 1985-1986; 210976 (Box 48)
  - "MASS" - panels 125-188, 1985-1986; 210977 (Box 49)
  - A.D. Christian Influence in contemporary society - poster, 1985; 210932 (Box 39, Folder 5)
  - Democracy Wall for Cardiff Posters, 1985; 210933 (Box 39, Folder 6)
  - "Messages to Washington" - America is beautiful bag, 1985; 210934 (Box 39, Folder 7)
  - "Rambo: First Blood Part II" Poster, 1985; 216163 (Folder 8 Right)
  - "Mass" Announcements - Newspaper: UTD Memory, 1986; 210935 (Box 39, Folder 8)
  - "Mass" Announcements - Newspaper: Los Angeles Contemporary Exhibitions, 1986; 210936 (Box 39, Folder 9)
  - "Anti-Baudrillard" - NAMIBIA in struggle - 1 of 3, 1987; 210937 (Box 39, Folder 10)
  - "Anti-Baudrillard" - NAMIBIA in struggle - 2 of 3, 1987; 210938 (Box 39, Folder 11)
  - "Anti-Baudrillard" - NAMIBIA in struggle - 3 of 3, 1987; 210939 (Box 39, Folder 12)
  - "The Castle" - sketched diagrams for shooting, June - September, 1987; 210940 (Box 39, Folder 13)
  - "The Castle" - Documenta [Exhibited Material] - Variety - Christopher Williams Advertisement, 1987; 211117 (Box 39, Folder 14)
  - "The Castle" - Documenta 8 Floor Plan [2], March 12, 1987; 216166 (Folder 17)
  - "Democracy" - Images for book - All People with AIDS are Innocent - poster, 1988; 210941 (Box 39, Folder 15)
  - "AIDS Timeline" - [Exhibited Material] - Department of Health material, [1987-1990]; 211118 (Box 39, Folder 16)
  - "Democracy" research - New York Times article - Talking Heads, 1988; 210942 (Box 39, Folder 17)
  - "Inserts" - Enough packet, 1988; 210943 (Box 39, Folder 18)
  - "Inserts" - Prince, Richard, 1988; 210944 (Box 39, Folder 19)
  - "Inserts" - Prince, Richard - originals, 1988; 210945 (Box 39, Folder 20)
  - "AIDS Timeline" [Exhibited Material] - Christian protesters photograph, [1988-1990]; 211120 (Box 39, Folder 21)
  - "AIDS Timeline" [Exhibited Material] - Dick Cheney and Ronald Reagan, [1988-1990]; 211121 (Box 39, Folder 22)
  - "AIDS Timeline" [Exhibited Material] - Gran Fury - "New York Crimes", [1988-1990]; 211122 (Box 39, Folder 23)
  - "AIDS Timeline" [Exhibited Material] - Health Care Quiz, [1988-1990]; 211123 (Box 39, Folder 24)
  - "AIDS Timeline" [Exhibited Material] - "I have Survived" poem and Chaka Khan poster, [1988-1990]; 211124 (Box 39, Folder 25)
  - "AIDS Timeline" [Exhibited Material] - Mike Glier posters, [1988-1990]; 211125 (Box 39, Folder 26)
  - "AIDS Timeline" [Exhibited Material] - Mounted photograph, [1988-1990]; 211126 (Box 39, Folder 27)
  - "AIDS Timeline" [Exhibited Material] - Sex Education photograph, [1988-1990]; 211127 (Box 39, Folder 28)
  - "AIDS Timeline" [Source Material] - Fight AIDS poster, [1988-1990]; 211128 (Box 39, Folder 29)
  - "AIDS Timeline" [Source Material] - photographs, [1988-1990]; 211129 (Box 39, Folder 30)
  - "Shopping Bag" - 3 shopping bags (originals), 1989; 210946 (Box 39, Folder 31)
  - "AIDS Timeline" Review - Matrix gallery - University Art Museum Newsletter, November 1989; 210947 (Box 39, Folder 32)
  - "AIDS Timeline" - [Source Material] - Child's drawing, [1989]; 210950 (Box 39, Folder 32)
  - "AIDS Timeline" - [Source Material] - Newspaper articles, 1989; 210951 (Box 39, Folder 34)
  - "AIDS Timeline" - [Source Material], [1989-1990]; 210948 (Box 39, Folder 35)
  - "AIDS Timeline" - [Source Material] - Act Up Chicago Ads, [1989-1990]; 210949 (Box 39, Folder 36)
  - "AIDS Timeline" - [Source Material] - general AIDS related Advertisements, [1989-1990]; 210953 (Box 39, Folder 37)
  - "AIDS Timeline" - The Artist's Response, 1989; 210952 (Box 40, Folder 1)
  - "AIDS & Insurance" Bus advertisement, 1990; 210926 (Roll-storage R4)
  - "AIDS Timeline" - "Evan photos for Hartford", 1990; 210954 (Box 40, Folder 2)
  - "Don't Mess With the U.S." Styroboard Poster, 1990; 216162 (Folder 1)
  - "Cash Prize" - Seattle Post-Intelligencer, 1991; 210955 (Box 40, Folder 3)
  - "Cash Prize" - Advertisement in full Newspaper - Seattle Post-Intelligencer, December 17, 1991; 210956 (Box 40, Folder 4)
  - "Cash Prize" - Final pieces in newspapers, December 18-19, 1991; 210957 (Box 40, Folder 5)
  - "Cash Prize" - Advertisement in Seattle Post-Intelligencer - Full newspaper, December 19, 1991; 210958 (Box 40, Folder 6)
  - "Cash Prize" - Advertisement in Seattle Post-Intelligencer - Full newspaper, December 20, 1991; 210959 (Box 40, Folder 7)
  - "Tomorrow" - Museum of Contemporary Art - San Diego, 1993; 210960 (Box 40, Folder 8)
  - "Brochure" - Text version layout, June 1996; 210961 (Box 40, Folder 9)
  - "Brochure" - Photo sheet - Group Material catalog, June 1996; 210962 (Box 40, Folder 10)
  - "Brochure" - Highlighted text version layout, June 1996; 210963 (Box 40, Folder 11)
  - "Brochure" -Three Rivers Arts Festival brochures, June 7-23, 1996; 210964 (Box 40, Folder 12)
  - "Brochure" -Three Rivers Arts Festival poster, June 23, 1996; 210965 (Box 40, Folder 13)
  - "Shopping Bag" - 3 shopping bags (reprints), 1997; 210968 (Box 40, Folder 14)
  - "AIDS Timeline" [Exhibited Material] - " All people are Innocent" Poster - Gran Fury, 1988; 211049 (Box 50, Folder 1)
  - "AIDS Timeline" [Exhibited Material] - Empire Strikes Back poster, 1988-1989; 211050 (Box 50, Folder 2)